https://www.celgard.com/privacy-policy/

Battery InnovationBattery ManufacturingMarketsElectric Drive Vehicles (EDV) ApplicationsExpertiseQuality & Environmental CertificationsAboutCelgard HistoryLeadership TeamWorldwide Celgard LocationsAuthorized DistributorsCareersLiteratureStoreContact
ENKRJPNCNENPrivacy PolicyClick to view our policy related to the Personal Information Protection Act ("PIPA") of Korea.This statement discloses the privacy practices for the Celgard.com website.At Celgard, we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to Celgard.com need to be in control of their personal information. We also want to present information on Celgard.com that is tailored to the needs of our visitors. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information when you visit certain areas of Celgard.com, download document files, or subscribe to a newsletter.We will use the personal information you share with us to ensure that the content, services, and advertising that we provide on Celgard.com (and related sites) are tailored to your current and future needs. If you provide Celgard with your mailing address or telephone number Celgard and its partners may use this information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and new products or services. If you provide your e-mail address, Celgard may contact you via e-mail. If you do not want Celgard or our partners to contact you (currently Celgard does not sell or rent personal information or e-mail addresses to third parties not affiliated with Celgard, LLC), you may opt out when you provide personal information or contact Celgard directly. For instructions, please see the Contact Us information below.If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still visit most of Celgard's website. However, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification.How Celgard Will Protect Your Personal Information
Celgard will protect the personal information that you share with us. If we request demographic information, we will not share information about you as an individual with any other entity. If we do share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.Celgard's Affiliates may send you information, by postal mail, about their products or services. If you do not want to receive information you may decline to receive it (or "opt out") when you provide personal information to Celgard, or you may contact us directly.Contact Us / How to Update Your Personal Information
You can help Celgard maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from Celgard, or our affiliates, contact Celgard by e-mail at
.(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address) or by postal mail at:Celgard LLC
Attn: Privacy
13800 South Lakes Drive
Charlotte, North Carolina, 28273, USAPlease include your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections.Celgard Would Like to Receive Your Comments and Questions About This Policy
Please address comments or questions regarding Celgard's privacy practices to us at one of the addresses listed above. Celgard may occasionally update this policy. Notice of revisions will be posted here.Links
This site may contain links to other sites and Celgard is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. Main linksBattery InnovationMarketsExpertiseAboutNewsContactLatest NewsCelgard Successful in UK Appeal Court, Keeping Injunction Against Senior UK Battery Separator ImportCelgard Success - UK Court Granted Injunction Against Senior Battery Separator Imports Through TrialPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseSitemap© Copyright 2018 Celgard, LLC. All Rights Reserved
Contact UsEnter your email to access the contact form.
Close Contact UsComplete the form and we will reply promptly.
First Name*
Last Name*
Email*
Phone (include country code)
Country*
Select Country
Company
How can we help?
